<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><title>programming on Gergő Vári's blog</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/tags/programming/</link><description>Recent content in programming on Gergő Vári's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.varigergo.hu/tags/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How AI automated my new project...</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/ai-content/</link><media:thumbnail url="https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/ai-content/thumbnail.jpg"/><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/ai-content/</guid><description>Imagine that you&amp;rsquo;re in a hopeless education system.
It&amp;rsquo;s all crumbling under its own weight. Outdated tools, outdated information
No one has ever told you anything about the real world.
You were only told that you needed to memorize this verse and that verse.
You&amp;rsquo;re also irresponsible and a terrible, unethical human being for even thinking your time is worth something.
You&amp;rsquo;ve been told you can&amp;rsquo;t schedule your time, but don&amp;rsquo;t worry; they&amp;rsquo;ll handle that for you.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine that you&rsquo;re in a hopeless education system.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s all crumbling under its own weight. Outdated tools, outdated information</p>
<p>No one has ever told you anything about the real world.</p>
<p>You were only told that you needed to memorize this verse and that verse.</p>
<p>You&rsquo;re also irresponsible and a terrible, unethical human being for even thinking your time is worth something.</p>
<p>You&rsquo;ve been told you can&rsquo;t schedule your time, but don&rsquo;t worry; they&rsquo;ll handle that for you.</p>
<p>We&rsquo;re not yet restricted in what we say, but does it even have any meaning to talk if no one listens?</p>
<p>That&rsquo;s the situation of the average Hungarian student. I&rsquo;ve got to take action; that&rsquo;s what I feel is for the greater good.</p>
<p>I first plan on helping my fellow students survive the current system until something changes. There are ways you can still excel at this system. You can even develop yourself while you&rsquo;re at it.</p>
<p>You see, many people use the system&rsquo;s quality as an excuse to do nothing useful in life. That&rsquo;s the worst attitude I could imagine.</p>
<p>Don&rsquo;t blame the game; blame the player.</p>
<p><a href="https://iskolahack.hu">Join IskolaHACK, a new and upcoming community for Hungarian students.</a>
(The URL might not be yet active; I&rsquo;ve got to get through some bureaucracy with .hu domains.)</p>
<p>My primary platform for this brand will be Instagram, as I know most of my fellow students use it daily. There&rsquo;s also TikTok, but more on that later.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/iskolahack/">I made a new project that utilizes OpenAI&rsquo;s new GPT and Dall-E 2 models for text and image generation. See the results for yourself on Instagram.</a></p>
<p>It took half a day, and it works very well.</p>
<p>I automated the text, the hashtags, and even the background image generation.</p>
<p>I still have the ability to curate and choose from variations; I still want it to have a soul.</p>
<p>AI will eradicate many jobs, but you should strive to fill the new roles that&rsquo;ll be needed.</p>
<p>Don&rsquo;t blame the game; blame the player.</p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>This small program changes EVERYTHING...</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/decentralized-websites/</link><media:thumbnail url="https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/decentralized-websites/thumbnail.jpg"/><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/decentralized-websites/</guid><description>Back when I was a young(er) kid, I remember that I always wanted to make a game. I was always ambitious—AAA Games, Open World, TPS, and all the other cool stuff&amp;hellip; Obviously, I never got that far.
The only options I had were shitty premade engines, Unity, Unreal Engine, and alike. Sure, the last two are very good options, but they&amp;rsquo;re not free as in beer or freedom. They go against all my values.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Back when I was a young(er) kid, I remember that I always wanted to make a game. I was always ambitious—AAA Games, Open World, TPS, and all the other cool stuff&hellip; Obviously, I never got that far.</p>
<p>The only options I had were shitty premade engines, Unity, Unreal Engine, and alike. Sure, the last two are very good options, but they&rsquo;re not free as in beer or freedom. They go against all my values.</p>
<h1 id="our-lord-our-savior">Our Lord, our Savior</h1>
<p>Meet Godot 4, the newest release of this 2D/3D game engine. It&rsquo;s always been said that open-source and free software is somehow worse in quality than for-profit programs. First of all, free software CAN be for-profit. Free licenses only require that you pass on the code to your buyer.</p>
<p>Second of all, if you check out Godot, it&rsquo;s got many features that are on-par with the big players.</p>
<p>I don&rsquo;t really feel like playing games anymore, and making them isn&rsquo;t very profitable either. Don&rsquo;t think that these engines can only be used for traditional &ldquo;games&rdquo;. Many programs require advanced graphics, and Godot is very extensible.</p>
<p>If you&rsquo;re really grateful for freedom, fight for it.</p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Will robots REPLACE US?</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/robots-replace-us/</link><media:thumbnail url="https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/robots-replace-us/thumbnail.jpg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/robots-replace-us/</guid><description>&amp;hellip; Deckard arrived at the towering Tyrell Corporation building, nervous about meeting Eldon Tyrell, the CEO and inventor of the replicants. Tyrell welcomed him into his lavish office and expressed his interest in seeing the Voight-Kampff test fail as a method to discover these machines. He asked the detective to try it on his beautiful assistant, Rachael, who appeared entirely human.
The Voight-Kampff test, designed to measure emotional responses, typically took about 20–30 questions.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>&hellip; Deckard arrived at the towering Tyrell Corporation building, nervous about meeting Eldon Tyrell, the CEO and inventor of the replicants. Tyrell welcomed him into his lavish office and expressed his interest in seeing the Voight-Kampff test fail as a method to discover these machines. He asked the detective to try it on his beautiful assistant, Rachael, who appeared entirely human.</p>
<p>The Voight-Kampff test, designed to measure emotional responses, typically took about 20–30 questions. Deckard’s attempt on Rachael took much longer than that. She appeared to struggle with certain questions, and her responses were erratic. He concluded privately with the CEO that her assistant was a replicant who believed she was human.</p>
<p>Tyrell confirmed the detective’s suspicions and explained that Rachael was an experiment, a new type of replicant created with a &ldquo;more human than human&rdquo; motto. She had been implanted with false memories to provide an &ldquo;emotional cushion&rdquo; and prevent her from realizing she was a replicant. Rachael had no knowledge of her true nature and had been living as a human for years.</p>
<p>Deckard felt uneasy about the revelation. He had always considered himself a hunter of non-human beings, but Rachael’s case blurred the line between human and replicant. He left the office, deep in thought about what it meant to be human and what kind of future awaited Rachael and others like her.</p>
<p>Based on Blade Runner&rsquo;s story</p>
</blockquote>
<p>As you know, I want to sell online, and I hate using centralized (and unnecessarily expensive) services, so I had to write my own small backend to handle Stripe payments coming in. The SDK is available in many languages, but for learning, I picked up Ruby. The problem is, it would’ve taken at least days to get up and running with my own code from scratch. Luckily, I’ve got an idea.</p>
<h1 id="the-feared-ai">The feared AI</h1>
<p>I went onto ChatGPT and told it to handle Stripe payments with Ruby and then send a request to Mautic with the payment information. It literally did it. No hassle, no nothing; I only had to do some touch-ups (and I obviously had to setup a VPS beforehand). Is it perfect code? Probably not, but I’ve never seen a human write something flawless for the first time.</p>
<h1 id="do-we-even-need-programmers">Do we even need programmers?</h1>
<p>Sort of. You see, at the moment, this is a great guiding tool. Yeah, it will surely develop. It will get to a point where I will tell it what to do, and it will even handle the VPS creation. Still, someone needs to supervise this process; heck, someone needs to tell it the goals.</p>
<h1 id="programming-is-dead-long-live-programming">Programming is dead. Long live programming!</h1>
<p>Traditional programming has ceased to exist. Isn’t programming just telling instructions to a computer (a very simplified description)? Just because we’ve made a (sort of) compiler that can translate English to specific instructions, that notion didn’t change. We’re just going to an even higher level than, let’s say, Python!</p>
<p>What I just outlined is still the future. For now, it’s a great helping tool.</p>
<p>&hellip; and I plan to use it. I’ve applied to Github’s student program to get free access to their new tool, and I also found a vim plugin.</p>
<p><em>UPDATE: Github doesn’t really want me in their student program, as I&rsquo;ve already been rejected. I’ll be sure to try again, but their process is very bad for smaller schools. Also, they could be clearer on the problems they&rsquo;ve had with my application. I can still test Copilot; there’s a 30-day trial.</em></p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>