<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><title>workout on Gergő Vári's blog</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/tags/workout/</link><description>Recent content in workout on Gergő Vári's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.varigergo.hu/tags/workout/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I've not even punched in my life before...</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/boxing/</link><media:thumbnail url="https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/boxing/thumbnail.jpg"/><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/boxing/</guid><description>1, 2, 1, 2&amp;hellip; I was at my first boxing session, and all I had to do was practice the six basic punches: jabs, hooks, and uppercuts (front and rear for all of them). The same motion, over and over again&amp;hellip;
Some might get bored of it, and some might get tired. I&amp;rsquo;ve felt both of those at the same time. Yet I did it and listened to all of the corrections my coach gave me.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>1, 2, 1, 2&hellip; I was at my first boxing session, and all I had to do was practice the six basic punches: jabs, hooks, and uppercuts (front and rear for all of them). The same motion, over and over again&hellip;</p>
<p>Some might get bored of it, and some might get tired. I&rsquo;ve felt both of those at the same time. Yet I did it and listened to all of the corrections my coach gave me. I felt great because I knew I had started a process. A process that will make me a fighter in the end.</p>
<p>Whenever you feel like giving up learning a skill because you&rsquo;re exhausted or unmotivated, keep going. It&rsquo;s going to be very rewarding.</p>
<p>At the same time, sometimes you&rsquo;ll have to realize you wasted time learning something unnecessary. Pivot is unavoidable.</p>
<p>Some might consider you a hypocrite for changing your opinion. Remember, you&rsquo;re a free agent. You control your state of mind. You&rsquo;ll have the humility to know when a change is needed.</p>
<p>P.S.: After my first session, all of my sleeping problems disappeared. Weight training alone isn&rsquo;t enough. Get some cardio in, too.</p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>