<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><title>personal on Gergő Vári's blog</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/tags/personal/</link><description>Recent content in personal on Gergő Vári's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.varigergo.hu/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to make sure you'll NOT get invited anywhere twice.</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/pick-your-assoc/</link><media:thumbnail url="https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/pick-your-assoc/thumbnail.jpg"/><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/pick-your-assoc/</guid><description>Imagine that I go to your beautiful place and break a few windows that you just installed.
Have you ever wished for someone to just turn on an annoying hair dryer for hours on your electricity bill?
If yes, you&amp;rsquo;re fucking insane. Hit me up, and I&amp;rsquo;ll make sure you&amp;rsquo;ll meet&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;my two fellows, who call themselves a certain, very liked ethnicity in Europe.
Let&amp;rsquo;s not mention the fact that they&amp;rsquo;re more white than me.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine that I go to your beautiful place and break a few windows that you just installed.</p>
<p>Have you ever wished for someone to just turn on an annoying hair dryer for hours on your electricity bill?</p>
<p>If yes, you&rsquo;re fucking insane. Hit me up, and I&rsquo;ll make sure you&rsquo;ll meet&hellip;</p>
<p>&hellip;my two fellows, who call themselves a certain, very liked ethnicity in Europe.</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s not mention the fact that they&rsquo;re more white than me.</p>
<p>They wanted to show off their &ldquo;light-skin rizz&rdquo; in the best light possible.</p>
<p>How do you even lose a freaking big vacuum cleaner?</p>
<p>The host was very happy.</p>
<p>We haven&rsquo;t been invited there again so far.</p>
<p>I don&rsquo;t want to lie; I had a little laugh.</p>
<p>Very little.</p>
<p>The moral of the story is: don&rsquo;t bring monkeys if you want to network.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m sure it&rsquo;s not a bad idea for a teenage party, though.</p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>I've not even punched in my life before...</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/boxing/</link><media:thumbnail url="https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/boxing/thumbnail.jpg"/><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/boxing/</guid><description>1, 2, 1, 2&amp;hellip; I was at my first boxing session, and all I had to do was practice the six basic punches: jabs, hooks, and uppercuts (front and rear for all of them). The same motion, over and over again&amp;hellip;
Some might get bored of it, and some might get tired. I&amp;rsquo;ve felt both of those at the same time. Yet I did it and listened to all of the corrections my coach gave me.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>1, 2, 1, 2&hellip; I was at my first boxing session, and all I had to do was practice the six basic punches: jabs, hooks, and uppercuts (front and rear for all of them). The same motion, over and over again&hellip;</p>
<p>Some might get bored of it, and some might get tired. I&rsquo;ve felt both of those at the same time. Yet I did it and listened to all of the corrections my coach gave me. I felt great because I knew I had started a process. A process that will make me a fighter in the end.</p>
<p>Whenever you feel like giving up learning a skill because you&rsquo;re exhausted or unmotivated, keep going. It&rsquo;s going to be very rewarding.</p>
<p>At the same time, sometimes you&rsquo;ll have to realize you wasted time learning something unnecessary. Pivot is unavoidable.</p>
<p>Some might consider you a hypocrite for changing your opinion. Remember, you&rsquo;re a free agent. You control your state of mind. You&rsquo;ll have the humility to know when a change is needed.</p>
<p>P.S.: After my first session, all of my sleeping problems disappeared. Weight training alone isn&rsquo;t enough. Get some cardio in, too.</p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>