<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><title>web3 on Gergő Vári's blog</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/tags/web3/</link><description>Recent content in web3 on Gergő Vári's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.varigergo.hu/tags/web3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>You're NOT ready for the FUTURE...</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/you-not-web3-ready/</link><media:thumbnail url="https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/you-not-web3-ready/thumbnail.jpg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/you-not-web3-ready/</guid><description>In one of my previous post, I touched on the fact that centralized services will inherently have a bias because they&amp;rsquo;re controlled by one entity. In our current Web2 world, that is a must: someone has to run the servers and pay the rent. That makes them responsible to higher-up entities (such as governments) to moderate their own platform. Under that disguise, it&amp;rsquo;s not surprising that people will project their agendas, willingly or not.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In one of my previous post, I touched on the fact that centralized services will inherently have a bias because they&rsquo;re controlled by one entity. In our current Web2 world, that is a must: someone has to run the servers and pay the rent. That makes them responsible to higher-up entities (such as governments) to moderate their own platform. Under that disguise, it&rsquo;s not surprising that people will project their agendas, willingly or not. I&rsquo;d prefer to at least see diversity in opinions, even though I have quite strong stances stemming from my personality.</p>
<p>So I wanted to future-proof my content and website, to be able to easily migrate to Web3 in the future. That would have the advantage of being decentralized, my site would be on many devices at the same time. Imagine that your favorite newspaper wasn&rsquo;t only available in one shop; rather, many trucks would load up and offer them all over the place. That first shop can easily disappear, but copies will stay up as long as there&rsquo;s demand for them. This is the next revolution in the information space, as big as printing became for manual book writing.</p>
<p>You think your weak little Wordpress site can survive this, but not so fast. You see, your site is probably dynamic.
Imagine going into the magazine shop, but you can&rsquo;t buy magazines; you can only use a projector to view them in
 the shop. Sure, great, but no one gets a real copy. The shop burns down, and so does the information. Yeah, you could take a photo of the projector, but it&rsquo;s tedious and often low quality.</p>
<p>Now, a static site generator works differently. It prints the book once from a template, and then in the shop you&rsquo;ll get another copy from that. You can distribute that anywhere, and however you like. Sure, with a Web2 backend, the printer can burn down, and we rely on the users to archive it all. But with Web3, there&rsquo;ll be no centralized shop. One truck will give out the templates to some other deliverers, and they can print more later. Information exchange will be almost unstoppable.</p>
<p>This will translate to lot CHEAPER storage costs, and EASIER content creation. <strong>As I said, you&rsquo;re NOT ready for Web3!</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://varigergo.hu/questionnaires/ask-web3-ready">My site is already static, and I can show you how it&rsquo;s done. If you&rsquo;d like to get started <span class="highlight">FOR FREE</span>, just click here!</a></p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>