<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><title>productivity on Gergő Vári's blog</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/tags/productivity/</link><description>Recent content in productivity on Gergő Vári's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.varigergo.hu/tags/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How AI automated my new project...</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/ai-content/</link><media:thumbnail url="https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/ai-content/thumbnail.jpg"/><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/ai-content/</guid><description>Imagine that you&amp;rsquo;re in a hopeless education system.
It&amp;rsquo;s all crumbling under its own weight. Outdated tools, outdated information
No one has ever told you anything about the real world.
You were only told that you needed to memorize this verse and that verse.
You&amp;rsquo;re also irresponsible and a terrible, unethical human being for even thinking your time is worth something.
You&amp;rsquo;ve been told you can&amp;rsquo;t schedule your time, but don&amp;rsquo;t worry; they&amp;rsquo;ll handle that for you.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine that you&rsquo;re in a hopeless education system.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s all crumbling under its own weight. Outdated tools, outdated information</p>
<p>No one has ever told you anything about the real world.</p>
<p>You were only told that you needed to memorize this verse and that verse.</p>
<p>You&rsquo;re also irresponsible and a terrible, unethical human being for even thinking your time is worth something.</p>
<p>You&rsquo;ve been told you can&rsquo;t schedule your time, but don&rsquo;t worry; they&rsquo;ll handle that for you.</p>
<p>We&rsquo;re not yet restricted in what we say, but does it even have any meaning to talk if no one listens?</p>
<p>That&rsquo;s the situation of the average Hungarian student. I&rsquo;ve got to take action; that&rsquo;s what I feel is for the greater good.</p>
<p>I first plan on helping my fellow students survive the current system until something changes. There are ways you can still excel at this system. You can even develop yourself while you&rsquo;re at it.</p>
<p>You see, many people use the system&rsquo;s quality as an excuse to do nothing useful in life. That&rsquo;s the worst attitude I could imagine.</p>
<p>Don&rsquo;t blame the game; blame the player.</p>
<p><a href="https://iskolahack.hu">Join IskolaHACK, a new and upcoming community for Hungarian students.</a>
(The URL might not be yet active; I&rsquo;ve got to get through some bureaucracy with .hu domains.)</p>
<p>My primary platform for this brand will be Instagram, as I know most of my fellow students use it daily. There&rsquo;s also TikTok, but more on that later.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/iskolahack/">I made a new project that utilizes OpenAI&rsquo;s new GPT and Dall-E 2 models for text and image generation. See the results for yourself on Instagram.</a></p>
<p>It took half a day, and it works very well.</p>
<p>I automated the text, the hashtags, and even the background image generation.</p>
<p>I still have the ability to curate and choose from variations; I still want it to have a soul.</p>
<p>AI will eradicate many jobs, but you should strive to fill the new roles that&rsquo;ll be needed.</p>
<p>Don&rsquo;t blame the game; blame the player.</p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>The NEW way of copywriting...</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/vyberd/</link><media:thumbnail url="https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/vyberd/thumbnail.jpg"/><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/vyberd/</guid><description>Yup, my site&amp;rsquo;s code was done. Checkout, funnels, posts, and everything else, yet something was missing. The actual content: copywriting isn&amp;rsquo;t my favorite activity to do, and I&amp;rsquo;m not that good at it yet. I never thought I would need this skill; after all, I aspired to be only a software engineer.
Now that I dipped my toes into marketing too, I often get into situations where I can&amp;rsquo;t write anything, even when bad copy would be better than none.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Yup, my site&rsquo;s code was done. Checkout, funnels, posts, and everything else, yet something was missing. The actual content: copywriting isn&rsquo;t my favorite activity to do, and I&rsquo;m not that good at it yet. I never thought I would need this skill; after all, I aspired to be only a software engineer.</p>
<p>Now that I dipped my toes into marketing too, I often get into situations where I can&rsquo;t write anything, even when bad copy would be better than none. If I put out something, at least there&rsquo;s a slight chance of making conversions.</p>
<p>What I&rsquo;m planning on is using <a href="https://github.com/vyberd">my Hugo Modules (which new subscribers got for free)</a> and making a tool to let me customize the colors and the copy. Where&rsquo;s the novelty in this? I&rsquo;ll make AI write the first draft of the copy. Obviously, I&rsquo;ll rewrite and change it to make it actually have soul. Still, a script template can go a long way.</p>
<p>Stay tuned for this. Also, I want to make my school life easier with AI too.</p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>