<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><title>diy on Gergő Vári's blog</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/tags/diy/</link><description>Recent content in diy on Gergő Vári's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.varigergo.hu/tags/diy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why I was LATE to a deadline...</title><link>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/modern-sites-slow/</link><media:thumbnail url="https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/modern-sites-slow/thumbnail.jpg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.varigergo.hu/posts/modern-sites-slow/</guid><description>I only had 20 minutes, and the deadline approaches. I quickly thought up ideas for my essay about that historical event. 10 minutes spent. I thought I had it all, I just needed to write it. I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to slow myself down by opening a text editor and then copying it into Google Classroom, so I decided to jump right in. BIG MISTAKE, KIDDO! &amp;ldquo;You need to login to your account&amp;rdquo; Yeah, sure.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I only had 20 minutes, and the deadline approaches. I quickly thought up ideas for my essay about that historical event. 10 minutes spent. I thought I had it all, I just needed to write it. I didn&rsquo;t want to slow myself down by opening a text editor and then copying it into Google Classroom, so I decided to jump right in. BIG MISTAKE, KIDDO! &ldquo;You need to login to your account&rdquo; Yeah, sure. &ldquo;What&rsquo;s your 2FA code?&rdquo; and &ldquo;We need to confirm your recovery address&rdquo;. LET. ME. WORK. 7 minutes left.</p>
<p>&hellip;then I &ldquo;quickly&rdquo; jumped into Classroom: 10 seconds just to see my classes, around 2 minutes just to get to the assignment. 4 minutes left; now I just need to open Google Docs: loading, loading, and loading&hellip; It didn&rsquo;t finish; I had to reload the document again. I had 2 minutes to write my actual essay.</p>
<h1 id="painful-to-be-productive">Painful to be productive</h1>
<p>Ah yeah, j-just let me open a big web app to send a message. Yeah-yeah, no rush: I&rsquo;ll just buy the latest CPU to get speeds that are ACCEPTABLE. Why do you even care about RAM usage? Every computer has, like, 64GB of it or what.</p>
<p>I despise this cowardly attitude: b-but it costs too much to optimize. No, it doesn&rsquo;t, dumbwit. Hardware is going in the direction of smaller and more efficient, so expect less and less RAM and weaker and weaker CPUs. Expect monochrome e-reader or RLCD displays to go mainstream. We&rsquo;re only going to get more minimalistic, so get on with the times and leave that idiotic Electron app behind.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;ll tell you what&rsquo;s the best and most productive interface: a terminal, a command-line. &ldquo;B-but that&rsquo;s not user-friendly; average people can&rsquo;t use it.&rdquo; So what? Average people can only use a mouse because they&rsquo;ve learned it. &ldquo;Just ummm, let me click 3 buttons that are each placed in different locations to do this one thing.&rdquo; I just can&rsquo;t and won&rsquo;t tolerate &ldquo;user-friendly&rdquo; interfaces.</p>
<p>I got into vim (my favorite and superior text editor), wrote here for a few minutes, pressed a few keys, and published the post to my blog.</p>
<p>Sadly, after that, I&rsquo;ll have to use the shitty Twitter interface; and actually wait for it to load. Ah yeah, all modern sites are slow just because we&rsquo;re putting unnecessary stuff in them. But that&rsquo;s for another day&hellip;</p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>